### Follow us:

### Follow us:

EatThis.com Privacy Policy
==========================

\[Eat This, LLC\] ("**Company**," "**we,**" "**us**," or "**our**") has created this privacy policy (this "**Privacy Policy**") because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared.  This Privacy Policy describes our information collection and use practices in connection with our website located at eatthis.com (the "**Website**"), and the services that are made available through the Website (the "**Services**").

By visiting any of our Websites, and/or accessing and/or using our Services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use.

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.

**The Information We Collect and/or Receive**

In the course of operating our Website, providing the Services and/or interacting with you, we will collect (and/or receive) the following types of information.

**1\. Contact Information**

When you contact us or our customer support team via the Website, email or by mail, when you call us, or when you sign up to receive our newsletter or updates about our articles, you will be asked to provide certain information which may include your name, email address, and phone number (collectively, the "**Contact Information**").

**2\. Other Information**

In addition to the Contact Information, we may collect or receive the following additional information ("**Other Information**"): 

* **From Your Activity.** In an ongoing effort to improve the Website, and the Services, we automatically collect certain information when you visit the Website, and/or access and/or use our Services. This information includes but shall not limited to, IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Site you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Website, and the Services ("**Activity Information**").

* **From Cookies.** We also collect Activity Information by using "cookie" technology. Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device to "remember" information about your visit. We may use session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer/device until you delete them). If you do not want us to place a cookie on your hard drive, you may be able to turn that feature off on your computer or mobile device. Please consult your Internet browser's documentation for information on how to do this and how to delete persistent cookies. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from us, the Website, and the Services may not function properly. 
* **Third-Party Analytics.** We may use one or more third–party analytics services to evaluate your use of the Website, and the Services, compile reports on activity (based on their collection of IP addresses, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, data and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Website you visit, number of links clicked while on the Website, search terms and other similar usage data), and analyze performance metrics. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By accessing and using any of the Website, and/or the Services, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website, or the Services.

Below is a list of analytics providers that we use; however, such list may be subject to change based on how we wish to understand the user experience and we will endeavor to update it diligently. You may use the accompanying links to learn more about such providers and, if available, how to opt-out from their analytics collection.

For Parse.ly, please visit: [https://www.parse.ly/privacy-policy](https://www.parse.ly/privacy-policy)  

**The Information Collected by or Through Third-Party Advertising Companies**

We may share Other Information about you with third parties that we have selected and approved for ad distribution and ad optimization (defined as the tailoring, targeting (i.e., behavioral, contextual, and retargeting), analyzing, managing, reporting, and optimizing of ads).  These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), and/or other technologies to collect Other Information for such purposes.  Pixel tags enable us and these third-party advertising companies to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which the pixel tag is located in order to learn which advertisement brings a user to a given site.  In addition, we may receive Other Information from advertisers and/or their service providers such as advertising identifiers, IP addresses, and post-conversion data. You may choose to opt-out of this type of tracking and sharing of information at any time by selecting the specific partners you wish to exclude from this website [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). You can also limit this type of tracking through the Do Not Track functionality in your web browser and a "Limit Ad Tracking" setting on iOS devices or a setting to "Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" on Android.

**How We Use and Share Your Information**

You authorize us to use the Contact Information and Other Information (collectively, the "Information") to provide our Website and Services to you, solicit your feedback, inform you about our products and services and those of our third-party marketing partners, and to improve our products and services.

Also, we may use and share the Information as described below.

* _Agents, Providers and Related Third Parties_. We may engage other companies and individuals to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf. Examples may include providing technical assistance, order fulfillment, customer service, and marketing assistance. These other companies will have access to the Information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law. We may also share your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, or other companies under common control with us. 
* _Aggregated Information_. In an ongoing effort to better understand users of our Website and Services, we may analyze the Information in aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve our Website and Services. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may use this aggregate information for marketing purposes. We may share this aggregate information with our affiliates, agents, business and business partners, and other third parties. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Website and Services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

* _Business Transfers_. As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, the Information may be part of the transferred assets.

* _Legal Requirements_. To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose the Information: (i) when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; or (ii) whenever we believe that disclosing such Information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of  Company or others.

We will take reasonable measures to require that any party receiving any of your personal information from us undertakes to: (i) retain and use such information only for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy; (ii) not disclose your personal information except with your consent, as permitted by law, or as permitted by this Privacy Policy; and (iii) generally protect the privacy of your personal information.

**Information Collected Through the Website that is Not Covered by this Privacy Policy**

You may voluntarily post and share information including, but not limited to comments, and reviews through blogs, forums and other similar features available from time to time through the Website. None of the information you provide through the use of these features is protected by this Privacy Policy including any personal information. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO ANY INFORMATION (INCLUDING PERSONAL INFORMATION) THAT YOU PROVIDE USING ANY SUCH FEATURES. ALL SUCH INFORMATION IS PUBLIC INFORMATION AND MAY BE VIEWED, COLLECTED, USED, MODIFIED AND/OR DISCLOSED FOR ANY PURPOSE BY US AND THE PUBLIC.

**Accessing and Modifying Personal Information and Communication Preferences**

You may access, review, and make changes to your personal information by following the instructions found on the Website, the Services or by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.eatthis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). In addition, you may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of any our marketing email. You cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our subscription databases. 

**Security of Your Information**

We take commercially reasonable security measures to ensure that your information is treated securely and is protected from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of such data, and in compliance with applicable laws and regulations. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Website, and/or the Services may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail or other electronic means. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure of your information.

**Links to Third-Party Sites**

The Website and the Services may, from time to time, contain links to external websites. We encourage you to review the privacy and security policies of any externally linked websites that may be accessed through the Website or the Services.  We assume no responsibility or liability for the information collection and disclosure practices of any external websites that a user can access through the Website or the Services.  Please check the privacy policies of these external websites before you submit any personal information to them.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect, receive, maintain, or use personal information from children under 13 years of age, and no part of any of the Website and/or the Services is directed to children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any personal information through the Website, and/or the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce this Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide any personal information on the Website, the Services, or any other web site without their permission. If you learn that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, you may alert us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.eatthis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases If we learn that we have collected any personal information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child's account.

**DO NOT TRACK**

We do not respond to or honor "do not track" (a/k/a/ DNT) signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

**Important Notice to All Non-U.S. Residents**

Our servers are located in the United States. Please be aware that your information, including your personal information, may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to use Website, or the Services, you do so at your own risk.  

**Notice to Nevada Residents** 

If you are a resident of Nevada, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of certain personal data to third parties. You can exercise this right by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.eatthis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject line "Nevada Do Not Sell Request" and providing us with your name and the email address associated with your account. Please note, however, that we do not sell personal data.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy and Practices.**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, so review it periodically. We will post any changes to the Privacy Policy on the Website and/or the Services, and the revised Privacy Policy will be effective when it is posted. By visiting the Website, and/or accessing and/or using the Services after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes.  Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or to report a privacy issue, please contact us in one of the following ways:

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.eatthis.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 5, 2022.

Footer menu:
------------

Follow us:
----------

Copyright 2024 [Galvanized Media](https://galvanized.com/). All Rights Reserved. Eat This Not That is part of the Dotdash Meredith Publishing Family.
